{
    "subject": "resource/In_convertendo_Dominus_(Rameau)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/In_convertendo_Dominus_(Rameau)",
    "human_readable": "The work 'In convertendo Dominus' by Rameau is the primary topic of this.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9803553819656372,
            "question": "What is the primary topic of the work 'In convertendo Dominus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8814651966094971,
            "question": "Who composed the work 'In convertendo Dominus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7071195244789124,
            "question": "How is 'In convertendo Dominus' typically performed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5452920794487,
            "question": "Are there any recordings or performances of 'In convertendo Dominus' available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5299137234687805,
            "question": "What type of musical composition is 'In convertendo Dominus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4879467189311981,
            "question": "What era or period is 'In convertendo Dominus' typically associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46363258361816406,
            "question": "Can you name any other works by Rameau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2024167776107788,
            "question": "Are there any historical contexts surrounding the composition of this work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19901804625988007,
            "question": "Is there a specific composer associated with this work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1822202056646347,
            "question": "What musical elements are characteristic of Rameau's style?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The work 'In convertendo Dominus' by Rameau is the primary topic of this.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2525_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific composer associated with this work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2525_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical contexts surrounding the composition of this work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2525_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other works by Rameau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2525_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2525_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss \"In convertendo Dominus\" by Jean-Philippe Rameau and provide various details about it, including its performance and style, confirming that this work is indeed the primary topic of the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}